every night
i dream the same dream
then
the nightmare begins
[Applause]
[Music]
hello people hello people welcome to
welcome welcome normal coder hello hello
and welcome and welcome this is nicolas
the dream of every programmer hello
people i want to show show show show
show you hello everybody what's up
people what's up people
what's up what's up what's up people
hello everybody on this video bye five
thousand subscribers
[Music]
you carry your gun mr chase
i never bothered ruins the line in your
suit
you used to be a spy
my child is a prisoner seventeen million
dollars oh they will take his eye is
near the hand and don't tell me you
don't have the money
my former father-in-law only buys the
best
it's time for you to do whatever it is
he pays you to do we need to pay the
rent
[Music]
because they put in the work so that
means that they actually take the course
seriously
and they
um they go through it they don't make up
excuses and they
foreign
[Music]
today i want to share with you my
experience it doesn't matter where you
go to university
those things don't matter it matters
what you do and that's how i learned by
doing i never said to learn just for the
sake of learning
everything that i learned is because i
needed to you are not a human being you
are a human doing